Next time you disappear without
telling us anything, you’re out of the gang.
When he was gone,
you were acting like a sad little puppy.
Like hell I was.
What’s that light?
That’s us.
We’re about to head out to sea.
Did you leave a note on my desk?
Do you think I should
study Sports Science like my senior?
Good idea.
That way, we can always stay together.
We’ve got the oranges, so we’re ready to go!
Orange.
Thanks for being my friend.
I won’t disappear again.
(Winter does not  only mean cool weather.)
Shake it harder.
Harder.
Why don’t you climb the tree
and pick them, Ko Neung?
When will we get to eat oranges
if we do this?
Come on. Keep shaking.
Come on. We almost got it.
(It’s also the symbol of our closer friendship.)
I arrived first.
Give me five baht.
(After we went on the boat trip,)
(the five of us became inseparable.)
Ko.
August.
It tastes so good.
It’s ripe enough to eat.
(We share warmth and laughter
while talking about things.)
(It’s an unforgettable moment for me.)
(What happened on the boat that day?)
Ko Song.
Look there.
Give me the blanket too.
Stop pulling it.
Hey.
Stop it.
Give it to me.
Ko, wake up. The sun is up.
Ko.
I want to sleep.
The school will open soon.
You need to adjust your daily routine.
No.
Come on.
Okay, I’ll tell your friend to leave.
Who is it? Augar?
Ko Song.
Why did he come here so early?
How would I know?
When you hear your friend is here to see you,
you get up right away.
But when it’s school day,
you’re always whining.
Mom.
What?
Give me some money.
Go take a shower.
But it’s cold.
Ko Song, please go home.
I’ll go now.
What a boy!
Do you miss me?
Is that why you come here so early?
Can you come to a plant shop with me?
I can’t carry it by myself.
What?
So you just need a laborer.
Didn’t you tell me that if I need help,
I can always tell our gang’s leader?
You are wicked, Ko Song.
I’ll give all the oranges on my tree to you.
Good deal.
Give me five minutes to take a shower.
Argh!
It’s so cold.
How are you going to carry a plant
on a bike?
Wait here.
Tada!
I don’t think it’s a good idea.
Why?
This is my dad’s sidecar motorcycle.
This is our chance.
My dad just came back from sailing.
He will be sleeping until the afternoon.
Why do you always
want to do dangerous things?
Are you saying no?
This is so fun.
Slow down. I’m not in a hurry.
You’re such a killjoy.
This is so fun.
What are you going to buy?
I’ll help you look for it.
Do you know anything about plants?
Give me 30 seconds, and I’ll find it.
My dad told me
to buy three Mother-in-Law’s Tongue plants.
Mother-in-Law’s Tongue?
Didn’t you say you could find it?
Boo!
Does this look like mother-in-law’s tongue?
Silly.
There, mother-in-law’s tongue.
Excuse me.
Are these mother-in-law’s tongues?
Yes.
How many ones do you want?
The plants are growing well.
We’ll look around a bit.
We’ll tell you
when we pick the ones we want.
Sure.
Hey.
We can’t just pick from what we see.
We need to feel the leaf.
The leaf should be firm, upright,
and fleshy like this.
If the leaf is leggy or drooping,
it means it doesn’t get enough sunlight.
The plant has many breeds,
such as dwarf or hybrid.
Why?
Don’t you believe what I said?
I believe you.
It just feels a bit strange.
Is that a compliment or criticism?
Neither.
My mom is a plant enthusiast.
I help her with gardening plants in my house.
You know how my mom is.
You’re surprised, right?
Yes.
Excuse me. We will take these three.
Here.
Thank you.
Do you want to plant an orange tree
in your house?
You seem to really like it.
I like the one planted next to my fence.
Let’s go. Shall we?
You need to choose
between holding on to the plants and me.
Don’t forget to wear the helmet.
Hold tightly. Otherwise, you may fall off.
Did I really see it?
Why am I always the only one who sees this?
He could just hold on to his shoulders.
Are your parents home?
My dad is.
He’s going to plant these plants soon.
You should put the bike back
before your dad finds out.
That’s right.
I’ve got to go.
My wage is one bag of oranges.
Okay.
I’ll take this.
That piece is mine.
Why didn’t you take other pieces?
There is no honor among thieves.
Hey!
I was eyeing that piece.
Why did you take it?
This one is yours?
Yes, I put my name on it.
I wish your mouth gets burned from eating it.
August, what’s wrong with you?
Why don’t you eat it?
Normally, you like to steal other people’s food.
He’s probably thinking about
the person who left him the note.
You are probably right.
So what happened, August?
Why have you been so quiet lately?
Are you keeping a secret from us?
No.
I’ve never kept a secret from anyone.
Don’t you guys dare keep a secret from me.
He’s delusional.
Let’s dig in.
If August is back to his normal self,
we won’t get to eat it.
Hey!
The new semester will start soon.
Time flies so fast.
I don’t want to go to school yet.
I still want to wake up late.
Why are you mentioning it?
You always wake up late
even when it’s a school day.
What?
Hey!
Why do you keep saying ‘hey’?
Why did you hit me?
I don’t want the school to start.
Don’t you want to become an adult?
No.
I want to be with you forever.
Is he talking about us?
Probably not.
I’m talking about you guys.
Let’s dig in.
Here.
Cut it out.
I heard that we need to join a club.
Why don’t we join the same club?
What do you think?
Which club should we join?
Let’s join the club
that doesn’t check attendance.
I think we should join different clubs.
Why do you want to do that?
You want to join the basketball club, don’t you?
Yes, but…
I agree with Augar.
We have different interests, Ko Neung.
That’s right.
Fine. We can join different clubs.
We are seeing each other in class anyway.
It’s not a big deal to be separated for two hours.
Don’t worry, Ko.
I’m not worried.
I’m chill about it.
The teacher is here.
May I have your attention?
It’s time to choose your club.
Have you decided?
It’s just a club.
I won’t go anywhere.
I told you.
I won’t disappear again.
Why aren’t we joining a club, boss?
I’m tired of it.
Everyone seems to have things
they want to do.
Why are you tired of it?
You still have me.
Augar joins the basketball club alone.
He will miss us, right?
He is just acting.
Augar, you pretend to be happy, right?
Stop it, August.
I may be the only one without goals.
Everyone knows what they like.
Look at Augar.
He likes sports. So he joins a sports club.
Ko Song and Achi like academic competitions.
So they work hard on it.
Even you,
who seems to have no goals like me.
But you work hard at the art and manga club.
Why don’t you join a quiz show with me?
I’m going to be serious now.
Listen to me.
I’m saying this as your friend.
We all have different interests.
You shouldn’t look down on yourself like this.
Many people out there
don’t know what they like or dislike.
My brother is going to turn 35 soon.
But he still plays Tamagotchi.
Your best friend, the porridge shop’s owner.
He opened the shop when he was 60.
That’s enough, August.
You make me feel guilty.
You are preaching to me
more than my dad does.
But I know what you like.
What are you talking about?
Promise me if I tell you,
you won’t be mad at me.
I promise.
That day on the boat,
what did you do with Ko Song?
See?
You’re not answering.
You like Ko Song, don’t you?
I saw you kiss Ko Song on the boat.
I’m just trying to think
what you’re talking about.
This is obvious.
So obvious.
I…
I knew it.
You like Ko Song, don’t you?
You are talking nonsense, August.
(I woke up to watch the sunrise.)
(I turned to look at him.)
(Then I reached
to take the flip-flop next to him.)
That’s all.
Don’t tell me that you’ve been acting strange
since we got back from the boat trip
because you were suspecting this?
No, I just…
Fine, I’m sorry.
I’m sorry.
Come on, August.
How would I know that?
I thought you had feelings for him.
What, August?!
I’m sorry.
I really want to hit you.
Fine. Hurry and follow me.
Maybe what he said is true.
Does it taste good?
It’s delicious.
Good.
You can help me eat it.
I can’t finish it by myself.
Why did you buy so many meatballs?
I was going to give some to a stray dog.
A dog?
I’m kidding.
I’m working on my jokes.
So I can keep up with everyone.
You’re ahead of everyone
with your meatball joke.
You don’t need to be so close.
Otherwise, Mr. Achi will complain
about my stinky sweat.
I’m already used to your body smell.
Where did you tell your chauffeur
to pick you up?
At your house.
That’s good.
I will have a company.
You should invite me
to your house next time.
I want to see your house too.
Sure.
You can sleep over if you want.
I can arrange a guest room for you.
You are joking, right?
What’s wrong?
No, nothing.
You are a bad liar.
I think…
I’m falling for someone.
Yeah.
That’s it?
Are you surprised,
or do you want to know who it is?
No?
I also have someone that I like.
See?
You don’t look surprised either.
If you really fell for someone,
you would have told everyone about it.
Right.
Today is our day, Augar and August.
We will win every medal.
I’ll compete in every game you are in.
I’m in. I will never lose.
You can compete in any games
that you want.
I won’t join you.
I’ll cheer on you from the sidelines.
But we are on different teams.
It’s okay.
I’ll cheer on the Red team.
I’ll be a spy.
Yay!
Let’s say this together.
Three.
Yay!
Damn it.
Why didn’t you wait until I finished?
Our timing is really off.
Let’s go.
Go where?
Let’s get our victory.
Yay!
You can do it, Augar.
That’s good, Augar. Keep going.
I’ll show you what I got.
Two points.
Time’s up.
Is he kidding me?
Ko Song, you can do it.
We are cheering you on.
Ko, go for it.
Come on.
The Red team is taking the lead.
- Come on. Faster.
- The Blue team reaches the finish line.
Are you okay?
Kids, can you make way for me?
Does it hurt?
A little.
I can’t put my weight on this foot.
You didn’t warm up before running, right?
No.
I was in a hurry.
A senior told me
that an athlete from Grade 10 was sick.
So I had to take his place in the race.
You need to rest for a while.
It will get better soon.
Thank you.
I knew it.
There’s no way that you would join the race.
Why didn’t you tell him
that you never compete in a race?
We were in a rush.
I didn’t want my team to lose points.
Ko Song,
you always put others before yourself.
This is a reward for a hero.
(The final football match
will begin in 20 minutes.)
(The Red and Yellow football teams,
please come to your booth.)
You guys should go.
I’ll stay with Ko Song.
Whether I’m there or not,
it won’t make any difference anyway.
But you are on the team.
I’m fine.
You should go.
Achi, you take them.
Otherwise, they will miss the game
and be hit by the seniors.
Let’s go win a medal for Ko Song.
But my team is competing against your team,
Achi.
I told you I’m a spy.
Come on, let’s go.
Come on, Ko Neung.
Go.
Are you okay?
I’m okay.
Go for it.
I’m fine.
- I’m fine.
- You should rest.
So I can read.
It was so loud there.
What is this?
Someone told me to give this to you.
It must come from the same person
who left you the note.
Open it.
I want to know what it wrote.
No.
I’ll read it alone.
Why?
Are you shy?
No, I’m not shy. No way.
Let’s see. Augar is having the ball.
He’s dribbling forward.
He shoots.
He scores a goal.
This Grade 10 footballer is the real deal.
He’s good at both basketball and football.
The Yellow team has the ball.
The Yellow team pushes forward and shoots.
Time is running out
- Time is running out
- But it’s not a goal.
I think Augar will score a goal.
I think Ko Neung will do it.
Where is Ko?
Okay.
Let’s bet on an ice cream.
It’s Augar again.
He is dribbling forward.
He is blocked.
Krittin has the ball.
He’s carrying the ball forward.
He scores a goal!
Augar! My ice cream!
The referee blows the final whistle.
The Red team beat the Yellow team by 3-2.
Well done, the Red team.
I told you not to skip the sports day.
See you.
If I find out who does that,
you will be in big trouble.
You.
The one who is facing down.
Hey!
Don’t you hear that I’m calling you?
Come here, Achi.
Damn it, August. That’s our friend.
I didn’t skip the activity.
Calm down.
I’m not scolding you about that.
I just want to ask you
if you are colorblind.
No.
Which team are you on?
Why did you cheer on our opponent team?
Huh?
They are…
my classmates.
So what?
Is it that hard
to stop being their friends for one day?
I promised them that I would cheer them on.
But you are on the Yellow team.
Bark for me.
Asshole!
Augar!
Don’t you do what anyone tells you to do?
Don’t you think this is too much?
Why are you so serious about this?
Sorry, the basketballer.
This is none of your business.
This is between the Yellow team.
I get it.
But aren’t you being too harsh on him?
If I said that to you, how would you feel?
Damn, I like you.
You are trying to be a hero.
So what are you going to do?
Your mindset is so bullshit.
What did you say?
Didn’t you hear it?
I thought I said it clearly.
Augar, calm down.
Back off.
You really got the nerve.
Do you want to try us?
I still respect you as my seniors.
But if you want to try me, then bring it on.
Hey, let it go.
He’s just a nuisance.
Don’t have a problem with a school athlete.
The teachers won’t take our side.
Let’s go, Achi.
Augar, you were so cool.
You didn’t care that they are our seniors.
You were ready to fight them.
Damn.
I thought I would be hit by them.
Thank you, Augar and August.
I feel like I’m a burden to you again.
It’s not your fault.
Those seniors were crazy.
But I caused you a problem.
Buy us ice cream.
Sure.
But I need to take a rain check.
I have to go home now.
What, Achi?
You need to buy it today.
You can go home later.
This is my house.
See you tomorrow.
See you.
Thank you.
Damn!
Why didn’t he hire a bodyguard
to accompany him 24/7?
He told me that if I slept over at his house,
he would arrange a guest room for me.
I thought he was joking.
Damn!
You did a great job today, Orange.
It’s a sure thing.
Do you also play football?
I’ve never seen you play it before.
Sometimes.
But I don’t like it.
Did you find what you like?
I like being with you.
What?
When I’m with you,
I feel happiest.
You are a safe zone for me.
Thanks.
What about you?
Do you like having me around?
Yeah.
But you annoy me sometimes.
Are you messing with me?
Why are you smiling?
What?
I’m not smiling.
How did you know that I’m smiling?
Can you go faster?
I’m hungry. I want to go home.
Okay.
You need to choose
between holding on to the seat and me.
My friend won the top spot today.
He won a gold medal.
Let’s go.
Can you walk?
Should I walk you to your room?
I’m fine.
I’m not crippled.
Now, he knows how to talk back.
See you. I’m going in.
Wait.
Here.
A reward for a hero
No.
You keep it.
You won the medal.
I really want to give it to you.
Just take it for my sake
Here.
Hold on.
I want to kiss the medal
to enjoy my victory first.
Here.
Thanks.
Do I look cool?
Wait here for a sec.
Why?
Why did he tell me to wait here?
This is your reward.
Damn.
So cute.
Thank you.
What?
I’m talking about this orange pillow.
Fine.
You should go.
See you.
See you tomorrow.
If you want to talk to me.
See you.
Don’t forget to take the bike inside.
(Come to think about it.)
(Our friendship is like a big blanket.)
(It turns our coldest moment)
(into a warmest memory.)
♪ I don’t know if this is love or not ♪
♪ I don’t know if you feel the same at all ♪
♪ Do you know I’m scared
and I don’t understand ♪
♪ How to handle the way I am? ♪
♪ Every time that we meet again ♪
(Yes, winter doesn’t last forever.)
♪ Something grows a little more each day ♪
♪ The closer we are,
the more I feel the love I’ve waited for ♪
(But the friendship that blossoms in this winter
will stay with us forever.)
♪ Even when winter fades I’ll still wait on ♪
♪ Till the final raindrop falls,
hope is never gone ♪
♪ As long as I have you holding my hand
as we walk on ♪
♪ I fear nothing if this season has you ♪
Are you wearing a perfume to school?
Look at you guys.
You’ve grown up.
You all grow in your own unique ways.
Ko Neung, did you find what you like?
This is our first trip together.
Do you like it?
Very much